well T Communications will be reporting
its third quarter numbers on January
19th now if you see compared to last
quarter the numbers are expected to be
subdued for the company now if you see
the revenue number that is expected to
increase by nearly 1% to close to
4,221 CR rupees but the AA number is
expected to decline by nearly 1.3%
margins are expected to decline by
nearly 70 BS points while the net profit
is expected to be down by nearly 2% to
close to 416 CR rupees for the company
in the third quarter of financial year
2022 now Revenue growth is expected to
be subdued because of a continuous
decline in the voice revenue of the
company but the analysts are expecting
the code Data Business Revenue to grow
compared to last quarter now the reason
behind this decline in the company's AA
and AA margins would be some oneoff
gains that the company had witnessed in
the second quarter of financial year
2022 now the company had witnessed a
one-off gains of close to 50 CR rupees
uh because of a delayed employee cost
recognition and because of of reversal
in provisions and because of this if you
see in the third quarter the margins and
AIT is expected to decline now the key
things to watch out for from T
communication earnings in the third
quarter of financial year 2022 would be
the order book growth that the company
has reported along with that the churn
levels that the company has been seeing
and any management commentary on growth
Outlook and price hike would be
important to watch out for from the T
communication earnings